<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
  <item>
    <quote lang="en">It's not the size of the dog in the fight, but the size of the fight in the dog</quote>
    <author>Archie Griffen</author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <quote lang="en">Nothing lasts forever. Not even your troubles</quote>
    <author>Arnold H Glasgow</author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle</quote>
    <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </item>
  <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Take chances, make mistakes. That's how you grow. Pain nourishes your courage. You have to fail in order to practice being brave</quote>
    <author>Mary Tyler Moore</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Being strong means rejoicing in who you are, complete with imperfections</quote>
    <author>Margaret Woodhouse</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us"> If you don’t go after what you want, you’ll never have it. If you don’t ask, the answer is always no. If you don’t step forward, you’re always in the same place</quote>
    <author>Nora Roberts</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us"> I've missed more than 9,000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. Twenty-six times I've been trusted to take the game-winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed</quote>
    <author>Michael Jordan</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">The only place you find success before work is in the dictionary </quote>
    <author>May V. Smith</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us"> Where hope grows, miracles blossom</quote>
    <author>Elna Rae</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Nobody can make you feel inferior without your consent</quote>
    <author>Eleanor Roosevelt</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">It took me a long time not to judge myself through someone else's eyes</quote>
    <author>Sally Field</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">I quit being afraid when my first venture failed and the sky didn't fall down</quote>
    <author>Allen H. Neuharth</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Hope never abandons you, you abandon it</quote>
    <author>George Weinberg</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Make the most of yourself, for that is all there is of you </quote>
    <author>Ralph Waldo Emerson</author>
  </item>
    <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Awards become corroded, friends gather no dust </quote>
    <author>Jesse Owens</author>
  </item>
      <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">People are like stained-glass windows. They sparkle and shine when the sun is out, but when the darkness sets in their true beauty is revealed only if there is light from within</quote>
    <author>Elisabeth Kübler-Ross</author>
  </item>
      <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Nothing splendid has ever been achieved except by those who dared believe that something inside of them was superior to circumstance</quote>
    <author>Bruce Barton</author>
  </item>
      <item>
    <quote lang="en-us">Life is 10% of what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it</quote>
    <author>John Maxwell</author>
  </item>
      <item>
    <quote lang="en-us"> Aerodynamically the bumblebee shouldn't be able to fly, but the bumblebee doesn't know that so it goes on flying anyway</quote>
    <author>Mary Kay Ash</author>
  </item>
</items>